{
  "card_id": "jj-mccullough-2026",
  "user_handle": "JJMcCullough",
  "answer_id": "cOSuuuIESN",
  "status": "active",
  "win_probability": 0.5,
  "target_win_prob": 0.5,
  "purchase_price": 1,
  "purchase_prob": 0.5,
  "created_time": 1768964409252,
  "grid": [
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "JD and Usha split up",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "IQ8hNACdsp",
      "answer_text": "JD and Usha split up"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "SCOTUS rules against DTJ on tariffs",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "qUsdqSSlII",
      "answer_text": "SCOTUS rules against DTJ on tariffs"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Maduro seeks exile in Russia",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "yPncSLRzls",
      "answer_text": "Maduro seeks exile in Russia"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Bessent made chair of Fed",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "pQS6q0sUuC",
      "answer_text": "Bessent made chair of Fed"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Full-length AI movie goes viral",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "A0s8U2qRzR",
      "answer_text": "Full-length AI movie goes viral"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Pro-Trump coup in Greenland",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "2EsINldccy",
      "answer_text": "Pro-Trump coup in Greenland"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Trump proposes 'Trump amendment'",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "PPOS6yIlQy",
      "answer_text": "Trump proposes 'Trump amendment'"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Hegseth replaced by Driscoll",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "5Rqd2psUPs",
      "answer_text": "Hegseth replaced by Driscoll"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Barron Trump does podcast",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "dOQszqyLnL",
      "answer_text": "Barron Trump does podcast"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "SCOTUS rules against DJT on 14th amend",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "UusccZhyU2",
      "answer_text": "SCOTUS rules against DJT on 14th amend"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "USMCA treaty torn up",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "yEcPOn8U20",
      "answer_text": "USMCA treaty torn up"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Deportation camp set up in Africa",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "6S9nOdzSUS",
      "answer_text": "Deportation camp set up in Africa"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "FREE SPACE",
      "prob": 1.0,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": null,
      "answer_text": "FREE SPACE"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Alberta separation referendum fails in landslide",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "lPERlsct8t",
      "answer_text": "Alberta separation referendum fails in landslide"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Fuentes speaks at CPAC",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "ECzPLSAqOc",
      "answer_text": "Fuentes speaks at CPAC"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Trump boycotts Biden's state funeral",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "9s62cRLu6s",
      "answer_text": "Trump boycotts Biden's state funeral"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Erika Kirk put in cabinet",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "RCLLZCEO80",
      "answer_text": "Erika Kirk put in cabinet"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Sir Keir Starmer resigns",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "0E5lN009uL",
      "answer_text": "Sir Keir Starmer resigns"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Nobel prize goes to US-led team \u2014 but not Trump",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "98gEpOIzy6",
      "answer_text": "Nobel prize goes to US-led team \u2014 but not Trump"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Trump suggests just printing money",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "sq6ZCOpQsn",
      "answer_text": "Trump suggests just printing money"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Justice Thomas retires before midterms",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "SqcSNn60nh",
      "answer_text": "Justice Thomas retires before midterms"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "PM Carney gets majority gov't of 3 or more",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "tz2CpQtuP0",
      "answer_text": "PM Carney gets majority gov't of 3 or more"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Trump sincerely proposes himself on Rushmore",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "A5nd9EAh2Z",
      "answer_text": "Trump sincerely proposes himself on Rushmore"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "New dance sweeps nation",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "2A8ySShqtC",
      "answer_text": "New dance sweeps nation"
    },
    {
      "slug": "jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Netanyahu loses election but gets pardon",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/jj-mcculloughs-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "SghIhLs0CA",
      "answer_text": "Netanyahu loses election but gets pardon"
    }
  ]
}